[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, screenwriter, professor and director of The Firemens Ball was born in \u010c\u00e1slav, Czechoslovakia.", "correct_answer": "Milos Forman", "incorrect_answers": ["John Malkovich", "Paul Verhoeven", "Wolfgang Petersen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Upon what does the loudness of a sound depend?", "correct_answer": "The amplitude of the wave", "incorrect_answers": ["The pitch of the sound", "None of these", "The frequency of the wave"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This song, composed by George Harrison, one of the members of the Beatles, caused a plagiarism trial.", "correct_answer": "My Sweet Lord", "incorrect_answers": ["Michelle", "Woman", "Love Me Do"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrayed Elaine Robinson, the woman Benjamin truly loved in the movie The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "Katherine Ross", "incorrect_answers": ["Tina Louise", "Paula Prentiss", "Nanette Newman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nights in Rodanthe is about a doctor who has an affair with a married woman. The stars also played a couple in Unfaithful. Who are the two leads?", "correct_answer": "Richard Gere and  Diane Lane", "incorrect_answers": ["Matt Damon and Franke Portente", "Matt Damon and  Minnie Diver", "Richard Gere and Julia Roberts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animals are used in the treatment of mood disorders such as depression?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Parrots", "Dolphins", "Dogs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A cats front paws have 5 toes and their back paws have 4.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The budget for the film The Blair Witch Project was only $50,000.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does a vexillogist study and/or collect  ?", "correct_answer": "Flags", "incorrect_answers": ["Stamps", "Bones", "Letters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Ghost, the name used by Whoopi Goldbergs character in the bank scenes was Rita Smith?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of food does Rosemary Woodhouse crave while she is pregnant with Satans child in the 1968 movie Rosemarys Baby?", "correct_answer": "Raw meat", "incorrect_answers": ["Human flesh", "Cat meat", "Lizard meat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The surface temperature of the Sun is 5,780 K, which makes it white.  Why does the Sun appear yellow from the surface of the Earth?", "correct_answer": "because of the blue color of the sky", "incorrect_answers": ["due to the electromagnetic radiation", "because of the distance the light travels", "because of our eyes inability to see light  in that range"]}]